A Guide to the Alfred E. Cohn papers, Rockefeller University Faculty FA132
Rockefeller Archive Center
- General Correspondence, 1
  - Stevens, A.R., 1941 1944 (Box 34, Folder 17)
  - Stewart, F.M., 1943 1945 (Box 34, Folder 17)
  - Stewart, H.J., 1941 1943 1945 (Box 34, Folder 17)
  - Stieglitz, Edward J. (Box 34, Folder 17)
    See Age Research club.
  - Stillman, E.G., 1941 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Stokes, James B. (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Strauss, Israel, 1945 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Straus, Roger W., 1945 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Streight, S.J., 1940 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Strunsky, Simeon, 1941 1944 1946 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Sturm, Max, 1940-1941 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Scheuer, Lewis M., 1941 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Sulzberger, Arthur Hays and Mrs., 1940 1945 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    See also Times, N.Y. and German Surrender.
  - Sulzberger, Marion B., 1940-1941 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    See also American Eagle Club of London.
  - Sulzberger, Frank L., 1942 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Survey Associates, 1940 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Swing, Raymond, 1943-1944 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Swope, Herbert B., 1941 1943-1945 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    See also Duggan, St., Emergency Comm. file and Times, N.Y.
  - Symers, Douglas, 1942 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - State of New York Board of Charities, 1927 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Stein, Fred M., 1922 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Stenström, Nils G., 1927 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Stephen, Karin, 1927 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Stewart, Harold J., 1923-1925 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Stillman, Edgar, 1923 1925-1927 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Strunsky, Simeon, 1927 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Sturges, Gertrude, 1926 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Swift, Homer F., 1924-1925 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    "Given to Miss Lingg Dec 28, 1960".
  - Steele, J. Murray, 1935 1937-1939 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Stafford, Jean, 1947-1949 1953 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - St. Regis Hotel, 1950 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Stern, DeWitt H., 1953 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Sternberger, Ludwig A., 1948-1951 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Sydenham Hospital [Undated printed matter and mss ] (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Taber, C.W., 1941 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Tanchester, David, 1944 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Taliaferro, W.H., 1940-1941 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Taylor, Floyd, 1941 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Taylor, Francis Henry (Box 35, Folder 8)
    See Metropolitan Museum.
  - Taylor, Dr. Graham R. (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Taylor, Howard C. Jr., 1941 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Teagle, Walter C., 1942 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - TenBroeck, Carl, 1940-1944 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Thorndike, Rosanna (Box 35, Folder 8)
    See Zinsser, Hans.
  - Thucydides (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Talmey, Arlene (Box 35, Folder 9)
    See Vogue.
  - Thomas, Henry M. (Box 35, Folder 9)
    See Physicians, Assn. Amer.
  - Telephone Company (NY) (Box 35, Folder 9)
    See Manhattan House.
  - Tamis, Lillian R., 1948 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Taylor, Harold, 1947-1949 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Tchelitcher, Pavel, 1952 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Temkin, O., 1946 1948-1949 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - TenBroeck, Carl, 1946-1953 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Thannhauser, S.T., 1945-1946 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Thayer, W.S. and S.R. Lectureship in Clinical Medicine, Johns Hopkins, 1950-1953 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Thayer, Charles, 1949 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Thorysay (?), 1952 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Tannenbaum, D., 1932 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Taussig, Helen B., 1928-1932 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Taylor, A.E., 1930 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Taylor, H.O., 1928 1930 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Taylor, Julia, 1928 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Thalhimer, William, 1930 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Thayer Memorial Fund, 1933 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Thayer, W.S., 1928-1931 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Thomas, F. Elizabeth, 1933 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Thomas, Karl, 1929 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Thomas, Carl C., 1928-1933 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Thompson, Norma S., 1930 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Thompson, Mrs. C., 1928 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Thorndike, Lynn, 1928 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Tiffany, Mrs. A.F., 1929 (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Tillett, W.S., 1929-1930 (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Tobacco, 1934 (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Trask, Lillian D., 1934 (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Trost, John Bud, 1928 (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Tull, Mrs. Samuel Oscar, 1930 (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Tannenbaum, Simon, 1923-1924 (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - Thayer, W.S., 1926-1927 (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - Trask, Miss, 1924 (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - Taliaferro, W.H., 1938-1939 (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - Tandler, W.S., 1937 (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - Taylor, Henry Osborn, 1936-1939 (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - TenBroeck, Carl, 1936-1939 (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - Thannhauser, Prof. (Box 35, Folder 13)
    See Emergency Comm. file, Applications.
  - Thompson, Mary B., 1937-1938 (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - Thompson, Dorothy, 1936 (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - Tobias, Channing H. (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - Trabert and Hoeffer, Inc., 1950 (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - Tree, Marietta (Mrs. FitzGerald), 1946-1953 (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - Turkel, Henry L., 1947 (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - Turkel, Ann Ruth, 1952 (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - Turner, Joseph, 1947 (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - Tilney, Frederick (Box 35, Folder 15)
    See Academy of Medicine, Library Comm.
  - Tillett, W.S., 1937 (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - Tilpon, Edgar (Box 35, Folder 15)
    See Wyckoff Memorial Fund.
  - Tinnin, Glenna S., 1938 (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - Tucker, Augusta, 1937-1939 (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - Tirana, Rifat (Box 35, Folder 16)
    See B.E.W.
  - Titiev, Oscar, 1943 (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - Tomkies, J.S., 1940 (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - Tompkins, Miss, 1940 (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - Toynbee, Arnold J., 1942 (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - Tozier, M.M., 1942 (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - Trachtenberg, Dusya, 1943 (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - Trager, Frank, 1943 (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - Treviranus, G.R. (Box 35, Folder 16)
    See Emergency Comm., file on Dr. Demuth.
  - Tucker, Augusta, 1940-1943 (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - Tuohy, E.L., 1943 (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - Trask, James D., 1923 (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - Truman, Harry, 1951 (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - United Medical Service, 1950 (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - University of Chicago Press, [General], 1940-1949 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - W.K. Jordan, 1943 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - University of Chicago Press, Miss Alexander, 1930-1931 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - University of Chicago Press, Mr. Bean, 1930-1932 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Mr. Laing, 1930 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Mr. Rubinow, 1931 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - University of Chicago Press, [Reviews and Clippings], 1931-1933 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - University of Chicago Press, [General], 1928-1930 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Ungerleider, Harry E., 1939-1940 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - United Air Lines, 1940-1943 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Umbscheiden, Augusta (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - United China Relief, 1943 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Vagts, Alfred, 1940-1941, 1944 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Vagts, Detlev, 1942 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - van Dyke, H.B., 1945 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Van Leyden, Ernst, 1940-1941 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Van Slyke, Donald D., 1940-1942 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Vineberg, Hiram N., 1943 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Vagts, Alfred, 1933 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Valentine, Mrs. Geneva C., 1932-1933 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - van Dyke, H.B., 1933 1935 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - van Leeuwen, W. Storm, 1932-1933 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Van Slyke, Donald D., 1933 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - van Tyn, Mrs. J., 1935 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Verney, E.B., 1929 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Victor X-ray Corporation, 1928 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Vinal, Harold, 1929 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Voegeler, W.J., 1934 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Vogel, Helen R., 1935 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Volhard, Franz, 1930 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Van Pelt, Elizabeth B., 1937-1941 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - van Doren, Irita (Box 36, Folder 7)
    See We Europeans and Heidelberg Pamphlet.
  - Vincent, G.E. (Box 36, Folder 7)
    See China Medical Bd.
  - Van Doren, Mark, 1943-1944 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Van Doren, Irita, 1925 1950-1952 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Van Slyke, Donald D., 1927 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Vincent, George E., 1925 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Veterans Bureau, [General], 1936-1939 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Veterans Bureau, [General], 1925 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Veterans Bureau, [General], 1926-1927 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Veterans Bureau, [General], 1924-1925 (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Veterans Bureau, [General], 1926 (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - Veterans Bureau, [General], 1927 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Veterans Bureau, Hawley, Paul R., 1945 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Veterans Bureau, American Veterans Committee, 1945-1947 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Veterans Bureau, Dublin, Louis I., 1939-1941 1944-1946 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Veterans Bureau, Langer, William, 1945 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Veterans Bureau, Griffith, Charles M., 1940-1941 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Veterans Bureau, [General], 1928-1931 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Veterans Bureau, 1928-1930 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Veterans Bureau, 1930-1933 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Veterans Bureau, Leslie T. Gager, 1930 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Veterans Bureau, Dr. Matz, 1928 1932 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Veterans Bureau, Capt. Munly, 1928-1929 (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Veterans Bureau, Dr. Munch, 1928-1929 (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Veterans Bureau, [General], 1935 (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - Vivisection legislation, 1947 1951-1952 (Vogue) (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - Vogue, 1948 (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - Wadley and Smythe, 1941 (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - Walck, Henry Z. (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - Waldo, Adelaide Price, 1943 (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - Wallach, Sidney (Box 37, Folder 14)
    See Atlantic Monthly, L.B. Fischer Publishing Company.
  - Wallach, Sidney, 1940 (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - Warburg, Dr., 1940 (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - Warburg, Dr. Bettina, 1943 (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - Warren, Constance, 1945 (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - Waterman, Max, 1944 (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - Watson, Robert F., 1941-1945 (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - Warburg, James, 1948 (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - Waverly Press/Williams and Wilkins, 1924-1927 (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - Waggaman, T.E. (Box 37, Folder 14)
    See Marshall, Supreme Court of the U.S.
  - Waddell, Mrs. Chauncey (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - Wagner, Joselyn (Box 37, Folder 14)
    See Flory, Dr. Wayside Gardens, see Nurseries, Iron Hill Farm.
  - Wayside Gardens (Box 37, Folder 14)
    Scope and Contents
    See Nurseries, Iron Hill Farm.
  - Wallis, Allen (Box 37, Folder 14)
    See Merrell, Margaret.
  - Wadley, Mary, 1938 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Wallach, Sidney (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Warburg, Bettina (Box 38, Folder 1)
    See Emergency Comm., Applications re Gerson.
  - Warde, Frederick, 1939 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Wadsworth, Augustus B., 1923-1924 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Wachsmann, S., 1932 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Wadley and Smythe, 1934 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Walker, D. Harold, 1928 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Wallace, George B., 1929-1934 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Warburg, Otto, 1931 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Warburg, Felix, 1929 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Warthin, A.S., 1931 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Welch, W.H. (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Wells, Edgar (Box 38, Folder 4)
    See James, Henry.
  - Wagner, Hon. R.F. (Box 38, Folder 4)
    See Soldiers Bonus.
  - Wearn, Joseph T., 1929 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Webb, Gerald B., 1928-1931 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Webster, Jerome P., 1933-1935 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Webster, Leslie T., 1929-1934 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Wehle, Harry B., 1935 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Wiseman, Esther, 1934 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Weiss, Soma, 1928-1934 1941-1942 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Weiss, Morris M., 1934 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Weiss, Victoria Brodkin (Mrs. Paul), 1934 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Weizel, Eugenie, 1931 1934-1935 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Wells, H. Gideon, 1934 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Wens, Gerhard, 1932 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - West, Randolph, 1933 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Weyhe, E., 1930 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Whedon, Charles C., 1935 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Weythe, E., 1930 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Whipple, Allen O., 1934 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Wearn, Joseph T. (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - We, the People (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Webb, Gerald B., 1941 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Webster, Jerome P., 1942 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Weed, Lewis (Box 38, Folder 6)
    See Contract, National Research Council.
  - Weeks, Edward (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Weicker, Theodore, 1940 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Weidenreich, Franz, 1939-1940 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Weinstein, B.B., 1942 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Weiss, Edward, 1945 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Welles, Sumner, 1942 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Wenzel, George, 1942 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Werner, M.R. [New Yorker], 1940 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Wertheim, H.M., 1944 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Weyl, Hermann and Mrs., 1944-1945 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Whipple, Allen O., 1941 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - White, Paul W., 1941 1943 1945 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Whittemore, Alice, 1941 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Whyte, John, 1940 1945 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Webb, Gerald Bertram ca, 1949 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Weinerman, E. Richard, 1950 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Weisenfeld, Shirley, 1949 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Weiss, Paul, 1946 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Weizel, Eugenie, 1946 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Weizmann, Chaim, 1947 1949 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Wendell, Mark, 1951 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Westermann, William L., 1951 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Weyl, Hermann and Mrs., 1945-1949 1952 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Wheeler, Edward C., 1951 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Whitmore, Carl, 1948 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Whitney, John Hay and Betsy, 1950 1953 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Weston, M. Moran (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Werrell, William, 1940 (Box 38, Folder 8)
    See Holman, D.V. file.
  - Weeren-Griek, H. van, 1950 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Wearn, J.T., 1927 (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Webb, G.B., 1925-1926 (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Weed, F.W., 1925 (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Weld, Theasea, 1924 (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Wertheim, Mrs. Jacob, 1922-1923 (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - White, James T. and Co., 1927 (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Weiss, J. (?), 1927 (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - White, Paul D. (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Webb, Gerald B., 1935 1939 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Webster, Bruce, 1936 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Webster, Jerome P., 1936-1937 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Weigert, Kurt, 1938-1939 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Weinberger, Bernhard W., 1936 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Weinman (?) [Theobald Smith portrait], 1939 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Weiss, Soma, 1939 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Wendt, Gerald (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Werner, M.R., 1939 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - West, Randolph (Box 38, Folder 11)
    See Journal of Clinical Investigation.
  - Whyte, John (Box 38, Folder 11)
    See Emergency Comm.
  - Weiss, Louis S., 1942-1946 1952 (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Welfare Council of New York City, [General], 1927-1933 (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Welfare Council of New York City, Mary C. Jarrett, 1936-1937 (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Welfare Council of New York City, Isidore Sobeloff, 1936 (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - Welfare Council of New York City, [General], 1936 1938 (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - Western Union [Telegrams to F. Frankfurter, E.R. Murrow, H. Laski], circa 1943-circa 1951 (Box 38, Folder 17)
  - White, Paul Dudley, 1914-1940 (Box 38, Folder 18)
  - Whitehead, A.N., 1941-1945 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Wilson, D.F.N. (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Winterfeldt, Fred M. (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Wilson, H.P. (Box 39, Folder 2)
    See Norton, W.W. and Co.
  - Williams, Dr. Horatio B. (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Wallace, Edith, 1953 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Wiesenthal, Alfred, 1953 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Willner, Otto, 1947 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Wilson, Thomas, 1953 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Winternitz, Emanuel, 1953 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Wood, Harrison F., 1953 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Wickard, C.R., 1941 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Wiegand, Dennis (Box 39, Folder 3)
    See Veterans Committee, American.
  - Wiggers, Carl J., 1943 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Wilcox, Herbert B. (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Wilder, Russel M. (Box 39, Folder 3)
    See Joint Distribution Comm. - Health Comm.
  - Williams, Horatio B., 1944 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Williams and Wilkins Co., 1942 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Willner, Otto, 1940-1943 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Wilson, Frank N., 1940-1945 1952 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Wilson, Julius, 1945 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Wilson, May G., 1940 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Wilson, William R., 1941 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Winlock, H.E., 1941 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Wise, Jonah B., 1945 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Wistar Institute of Anatomy and Biology, 1940 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Wile, Edith L. (Mrs. Walter), 1924-1925 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Wile, Udo J., 1925-1926 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Wynne, Shirley W., 1926 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Williams, H.B., 1924 1927 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Wilson, Frank N., 1923-1927 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Winterberg, H., 1927 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Wistar Institute of Anatomy and Biology, Press of, 1925 1928 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Willert, Paul, 1936-1939 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Williams, William R. (Box 39, Folder 5)
    See Jessup, Ph.
  - Willner, Otto, 1936-1939 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Wilson, May G., 1937-1938 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Winslow, C.-E.A., 1936 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Winternitz, M.C., 1938 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Wiggers, C.J., 1930-1932 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Wignall, E.W., 1931 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Wilce, J.W., 1929 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Wilinsky, Charles F., 1932 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Williams, Margaret J., 1930-1931 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Williams, H.B., 1929 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Williams, Linsly R., 1930 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Williams and Wilkins Co., 1928 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Willner, Otto, 1929-1930 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Wilson, Frank N., 1928-1934 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Wilson, George Wade, 1929 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Wilson, May G., 1930-1935 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Wilson, James R., 1928 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Wilt, A.D., 1928 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Winternitz, M.C., 1928 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Wistar Institute of Anatomy and Biology, 1931 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Wood, Robert E., 1940 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Woodruff, I.O., 1940 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Woodworth, William, 1940 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Woody, McIver, 1941 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Woollcott, Alexander, 1941 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Worden, Helen, 1944 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Worley, Mr., 1941 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Worster, Harry Pray, 1940 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Wright, Irving S., 1940 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Wulman, L. (Box 39, Folder 7)
    See Joint Distribution Comm.
  - Wyckoff, Elizabeth and Betsy, 1944 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Wyzanski, Charles, 1943 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Wood, Harrison F., 1949 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Woolley, D.W., 1948 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Worster, Harry Pray, 1946 1951 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Wulff, Christine, 1947 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Wyckoff, Betsy, 1948 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Woodhouse, Mrs. T.F. (Box 39, Folder 8)
    See Burroughs, Betsy.
  - Wood, J. Edwin, 1923-1925 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Woodcock, (Miss), 1925-1926 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Woodruff, I. Ogden, 1926 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Woodberry, George E., 1925 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Woodyatt, Rollin T., 1924 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Wright, Jonathan, 1923 1926 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Wyckoff, John, 1924-1927 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Wolferth, Charles C., 1929 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Wood, Susan M., 1930 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Woodger, J.H., 1930 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Woodruff, I.O., 1933-1934 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - World Peace Foundation, 1932-1935 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Wright, Helen M., 1934 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Wright, Jonathan, 1928 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Wu, C.J., 1934 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Wu, Hsien, 1933 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Wyckoff, John, 1928-1935 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Wyckoff, Ralph W.G., 1931 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Wyllie, J., 1932 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Wynne, Shirley, 1929 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Woodruff, I. Ogden, 1937 1939 (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - Wrinch, Dorothy, 1936-1938 (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - Wright, Helen M., 1939 (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - Wyckoff, John (Mrs.), 1937-1939 (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - Yale University, 1947 (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - Yale Review, 1946 (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - Yardumian, K. [and Kleinerman, J.], 1949 (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - Zacco, Dr., 1949 (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - Zeigler, Oscar (Mrs.), 1946 (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - Zuckerman, Solly, 1952 (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - Zemurray, Samuel, 1950 (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - Zachry, Caroline, 1939 1945 (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - Yarrow, Clarence H., 1943 (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - Yarrow, William, 1941 (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - Yerkes, Robert M., 1945 (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - Zinsser, Hans, 1940 (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - Zale, Elizabeth, 1940 (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - Zinsser, Hans, 1928-1929 (Box 39, Folder 14)
- Biographical material, 2; (5" Letter) (Box 40)
  - Bibliographies
    - Assorted versions (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - Ruth Sternfeld's Archives bibliography for AEC Collected Reprints (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - Department of Clinical Physiology, circa 1908-1955 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Biographical articles etc.
    - Chronology, 10 pp, 1960 (Box 40, Folder 4)
      See also copy and covering letter in Correspondence, administrative.
    - Cranefield, Paul F. Article on AEC for Dictionary of American Biography, Supplement 6, 1980 (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - Horsfall, Frank L. Jr. Article on AEC for Rockefeller Institute Quarterly, 1957 September (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - Manuscripts and notes (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - Obituaries (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Clippings (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, administrative, 1911-1960, undated
    - 1911-1919 (Box 40, Folder 10)
    - 1920-1922 (Box 40, Folder 11)
    - 1923-1925 (Box 40, Folder 12)
    - 1926-1929 (Box 40, Folder 13)
    - 1930-1939 (Box 40, Folder 14)
    - 1940-1942 (Box 40, Folder 15)
    - 1943-1949 (Box 40, Folder 16)
    - 1950-1954 (Box 40, Folder 17)
    - 1957 (Box 40, Folder 18)
    - 1960, undated (Box 40, Folder 19)
  - Rockefeller Institute/University. Subjects
    - Assistants, 1940-1944 (Box 40, Folder 20)
    - Board of Scientific Directors, 1942 1944 (Box 40, Folder 21)
    - Electrocardiograph history (Box 40, Folder 22)
    - Inventory of apparatus and materials brought to RIMR by AEC, 1911 (Box 40, Folder 23)
    - 60th birthday, 1939 (Box 40, Folder 24)
    - Teachers Insurance and Annuity Association, 1944 (Box 40, Folder 25)
- Photographs and prints, 3; 5 folders, 2.5" Letter
  - Portraits of A.E. Cohn
    - 1923 (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - 1932 (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - 1937 (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - 1945 (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - undated (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Group photos (Box 41)
    See also oversize.
    - World War I. American Expeditionary Force officers? (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - AEC with students at Peking Union Medical College, 1925. Signed and inscribed (Box 41, Folder 7)
    - Columbia University D. Sc. degree, 1940; [print scratched] (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Mackenzie, Sir James (Box 41, Folder 8)
    Includes photos with AEC.
  - People (Box 41)
    - Identified. J. Willard Gibbs [German postcard print]; Hideyo Noguchi (Box 41, Folder 9)
    - Prints of portrait paintings (Box 41, Folder 10)
      Includes Lafayette B. Mendel, Lavoisier and Mrs. Lavoisier (J. David), Sir Henry Dale, Eugene L. Opie, William Hallock Park, Prof. Starling.
    - Unidentified (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - AEC apartment interiors (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - People. "Galerie Hervorragender Arzte und Naturforscher", 1910-1911; Some prints damaged (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Laboratory/Technical (Box 42)
    See also RUA collection of Lab photos.
    - Record racks for EKG recordings, 1926 (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - Diagrams of lab. layout, circa 1928 (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - Research/technical, miscellaneous (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Landscapes (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Malpighi, Marcellus. Photographic snapshots of various Malpighi-related buildings, memorabilia, etc. Gift of Prof. Franchini to AEC (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Palestine [canals], 1928 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Peking Union Medical College. Ground plan, 1925 (Box 42, Folder 8)